

PROGRAMMER ANALYST

□ (+1) 310-941-3409 | **I** kmng73@gmail.com | **I** kmng | **I** stefantopia | **I** @stefantopia

Professional Summary

Web Application Developer with 15 years of experience designing and implementing solutions in the health care industry. Brings strong expertise in various application platforms, design patterns and development paradigms. Committed to following industry best practices, maintaining communication with customers and establishing long-term maintainability of the products. Known for developing exceptional applications from beginning to end.

Skills_

Programming Java, Groovy, PHP, Javascript, TypeScript, Python, C, C++, C#, VB.NET, SQL, HTML, CSS, Bash, ŁTFX

Web Grails, Laravel, Angular, React, ¡Query

Databases MySQL, Access, SQLite, MS SQL server ,MongoDB **Servers** Linux, Window Server, AWS, Docker, Puppet

Management Project Management

Work Experience

Department of Radiological Sciences, UCLA

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST IV

Aug 2018 - Present

System Architect and Technical Lead

- Provide technical leadership to two large scale projects
- Design system architecture Design for next generation of Faculty academic productivity metrics application (aRVU) using latest services based architecture to improve agility and performance. The application is implemented using RESTful API backend with Java/Grail environment and Spring Framework and Single Page Application Frontend with JavaScript/Typescript environment and Angular 7 framework
- Establish implementation and release plan to enable rapid development cycle, improve adaptation to requirements changes and allow increase development velocity. This allow rapid re-implementation of all existing features together with implementation of 2021 new metrics in shorten time
- Collaborate with UCLA Health IT system operation team using Puppet to provision both development and production environment to ensure stability of the application

Technical Mentorship and Project Management

- Mentor and delegate work assignments to a Programmer/Analyst III
- Provide project management expertise and set up team project management environment using GitLab platform to promote collaboration and improve team communication

Department of Radiological Sciences, UCLA

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST III

NALYST || Dec 2015 - Aug 2018

Academic Relative Value Unit (aRVU) Initiative

- Design and Develop aRVU Application to generate academic performance metrics of faculty academic productivity of 100 faculties in department of Radiology to support academic personnel decisions like bonuses and promotions using Java/Grails environment with Spring Framework
- Integrating multiple internal and external data sources using automation to elmintate human data entry error
- Create user-friendly UI for more than 100 faculties, administrative assistants, fund managers, clinical trials study coordinators and department executive to enhance data accuracy and efficiency
- Application showcase in multiple cross-UC conferences to highlight usage of aRVU

Research Imaging Service (RIS) Application

- Design and Develop Web-based Application to handle clinical trials requests from the whole institution to the department using PHP/MySql environment with Laravel Framework
- • The application is known as the golden standard for clinical trial management system in usability and functionality

School of Engineering Distance Learning Network, USC

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST III

Dec 2012 - Dec 2015

- Collaborate with a team of developers to design and develop online learning environment and supporting tools using PHP with Oracle backend
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Design and Develop internal administration tools to support students}\ , faculty\ and\ administrators\ in\ the\ remote\ learning\ environment$

APRIL 4, 2021 STEPHEN NG · RÉSUMÉ

Dept of Medicine, UCLA Medical Center

Los Angeles, CA USA

SR. INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST

Sep 2009 - Dec 2012

- Design and Develop patient medical records and data collection system for the Dept. of Medicine (DOM) outpatient program, as well as the hospital's internal medicine and urgent care facilities
- Manage all web-based systems for DOM Education Office to meet various departmental needs
- Design and develop a web-based, HIPPA compliant physician note system that readily permits exchange of information between primary physicians, consultants and other care providers, as well as rapid recoding of necessary data for record-keeping
- Support, maintain and expand existing medical reminder system to tract therapies, needed diagnostic studies, follow-ups, appointment, etc for monitoring of patient's care processes
- · Create and develop a secure online patient-physician email based corresponding and prescription system
- Perform ongoing project development and site maintenance functions for various DOM websites

Dept of Medicine, UCLA Medical Center

Los Angeles, CA USA

Jun 2003 - Sep 2009

PROGRAMMER/ANALYST II

- Design, Develope and Maintaine Web solution for the Department of Medicine
- Develope Enterprise Patient Record and Preventive Screening Reminder (Expert) System (Outpatient Signout) with connection to MCCS web services
- Design and maintain Website for Department of Medicine (Housestaff and Schedules)
- Construct and Design the Website portal for Dept. of Medicine
- · Construct multi-hosts testing environment using SME server (customized Red Hat 7.3 Linux server)
- · Develop and maintain various websites in the Department of Medicine including Office of Research Administration Website

Education

UCLA Extension, Los Angeles

Los Angeles, CA USA

PROJECT MANAGEMENT CERTIFICATION

University of Califonia, Los Angeles

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Los Angeles, CA USA 2004

• GPA 3.8

University of Califonia, Los Angeles

Los Angeles, CA USA

M.S. IN PHYSICS

2001

• GPA 3.8

Chinese University of Hong Kong

Chinese University of Hong Kong

Hong Kong, Hong Kong

M.S. IN PHYSICS

• GPA 3.8

B.S. IN PHYSICS

Hong Kong, Hong Kong

• GPA 3.7

Professional Development

Profesional Development Program

Los Angeles, CA USA

UCLA 2019

APRIL 4, 2021 STEPHEN NG · RÉSUMÉ 2